You've been summoned
by an investigative committee?
Yes.
Deborah Darkian, is it?
I summon you to the Starlight Room
at the Grand Merillian for investigation.
This isn't legally enforceable.
I don't see why you should play along.
I take it you're going?
I'm certain there's much more
I need to learn.
Do you know what they call
Deborah's investigative committee?
Their gatherings are famous,
but no one knows what transpires there.
No one will breathe a word.
So it has acquired the name...
the Silent Ladies' Tea Party.
Welcome, Constance Grail.
I see your head is still attached.
While I assume you're aware,
you are not to speak of anything
that happens here.
Do you still wish to proceed?
That won't be a problem.
These three are Deborah's hangers-on.
The thing is, I received a letter
from your friend, Pamela Francis.
From Pamela?
The poor dear. I hear her hair
has turned white as snow.
But she wrote saying that
nothing you did broke the law.
So you see, someone else
must step in to review your crimes.
My crimes?
We mean to say we'll do you
the honor of judging you.
You wouldn't want to end up like
Scarlett Castiel, now would you?
Scarlett?
It was simply dreadful.
That face she was so proud of,
rolling through the mud like some toy...
Everyone—yes, even the most lowly—
clapped and laughed and jeered.
I know I could never bear the shame
of such an ignominious end.
What do you think you're doing?
Holding my hand?
Up till now, we've switched
so she could save me.
But not this time.
We're going...
to fight together!
This is a tawdry farce,
but I'll play along.
I beg your pardon?
Didn't you hear me? Listen well.
I said that I...
that we are going to judge you!
Oh?
The Earl John Doe Ball must have been
quite a blow to you, Deborah Darkian.
You speak of the dancing children?
With all due respect, it was I
who reported them to the Security Force.
To think we had human
traffickers in our midst!
The mere thought makes my blood run cold.
And why did everyone there
have ties to the Darkians, I wonder?
Take the Marquess of McLain,
who looked so friendly with the slavers.
Esther,
I mean your husband.
I doubt he'll be able to avoid prison.
Then again,
he may receive a lighter sentence
if he were to name the ringleader.
Surely you know of my fiancé's position.
Depending on your testimony, I would
be happy to put in a good word with him.
Okay.
We've as good as won.
I leave the rest to you.
Thank you, Scarlett.
The Marchioness of McLain must know
Deborah Darkian had a hand in the crime.
If I can get her to attest to that...
Ladies.
Did you hear something just now?
Oh, that reminds me.
Wasn't the Marquess of McLain
just about to leave the country?
Am I wrong, Esther?
He won't be back for some time, will he?
Th-That's right.
What's going on?
You still don't see?
Did you seriously imagine a viscount's
daughter could crush a Darkian?
Now, I think it's time we took a vote.
Who should be judged here, you or me?
This isn't good.
Under the circumstances...
Of course, if you bend the knee
to me like a good little girl,
I might decide Pamela
was only imagining things.
How dare she?!
Now, have you anything
to say for yourself?
I... I...
Yes?
I...
don't agree with your methods one jot!
They can do what they will with me.
I refuse to back down now!
You little—
Why, hello there! Do pardon the intrusion.
Honestly.
They kept pestering me about formalities,
and now look how late it's gotten!
How rude of you to barge in uninvited,
Abigail O'Brian.
The four great noble families
of our kingdom are the Castiels,
the Richelieus, the Darkians, and...
How do you do, young lady?
This woman...
She's an O'Brian!
Um, that's...
Susannah Neville's seat, yes.
I'm here in her place.
Here. My credentials.
Th-Then, if you'd sign here...
I have only one thing to say.
Esther. Janine.
Caroline.
Unless you want to be crushed,
do as I say.
Really, Abigail.
That sounded like a threat.
If you insist on menacing my friends,
I must have legal recourse.
We can't have that, Debbie.
Nothing said here leaves this room.
You made that rule yourself.
Forgive me.
I don't feel at all well.
You must excuse me early today.
Really, dear, you mustn't
take such thoughtless risks.
No quarter is given in our world.
Um... Thank you very much.
You'd best save your thanks
for Randolph Ulster.
Why His Lordship?
Yesterday, he came calling at my house
and asked me to help his fiancée
because she seemed likely
to poke her nose into trouble.
He'd looked into the participants here
and acquired this letter for me.
Why do I feel so, I don't know...
warm and fuzzy?
Constance Grail?!
I knew it!
Say, could you spare me a few words?
Er, um, who might you—
When did you start looking up
to Scarlett Castiel?
Are you rebelling against the famous
Grail family ideal of sincerity?
Did you tire of being a good girl?
Must've been frustrating when the papers
all focused on Teresa Jennings's death.
Huh? Wh-Who's Teresa?
You don't remember? She was half
of that scene at Emilia's ball.
Oh, her!
Why, didn't you know?
The man she was having
an affair with broke it off,
and she tried to kill him
when she took her own life.
You mean she's...
But enough about that! How do you
and your fiancé, Randolph Ulster—
Don't you think that's enough, Amelia?
Aldous!
The editor in chief said he'd demote you
if you do any more unscheduled interviews.
Until next time, Constance Grail!
I have every faith
you'll answer sincerely, of course!
So she's a reporter?
Good grief.
Please forgive me colleague.
Oh, no need.
I'm Aldous Clayton,
with the Mayflower Company.
Do let me know if Amelia
causes you any more bother.
Th-Thank you.
What was that about?
Just think of her as a cat
that happened to scratch at you.
"Miss C., the daughter of a viscount,
emulates the infamous Scarlett Castiel."
"She indulges in now-banned hallucinogens
and spends her days in wild orgies."
It's nonsense! Awful hogwash!
Well, of course it is.
What a shame. And here I was, looking up
to Amelia Hobbes as a role model.
A role model? Her?
Didn't I tell you?
My dream is to stay unmarried
and become a reporter.
Is it really?
You told me yourself.
I've always been obsessed
with chasing rumors,
so you said, "If you enjoy it so,
why not become a reporter?"
No one else would suggest such a thing
to me at the time, even as a joke.
It felt like you truly saw me.
I was delighted.
Really?
Now, you're having tea with
Crown Princess Cecilia later, right?
I expect a juicy scoop!
Oh, right...
May I have a moment of your time?
I represent the Ladies' Committee
of the Violet Association.
Kimberly Smith is my name.
What now?
We are working to rid our land
of inhumane culture.
I've come to remonstrate with the foolish
young lady who idolizes Scarlett Castiel.
I want to leave.
This bit about hallucinogens
in particular.
Don't tell me it's referring
to Jackal's Paradise.
Jackal's Paradise?
Speaking of Jackal's Paradise...
Where do you think you're looking?
You don't want the likes
of me in your sight?
How very aristocratic.
You bigots don't even consider
us common folk human.
I d-don't think that's fair to—
Are my parents bigots too, then?
Kate!
Aren't you the Lorraines' daughter?
I come from a baronial family,
but my mother was born a commoner.
Are we still bigots simply
because we're of the nobility?
I'm afraid you must excuse me for today.
Kate, thank y—
Is it true you got engaged
to the Earl of Ulster?
Well...
So it is true.
You won't tell me anything?
I know I said I'd wait for you to open up,
but that doesn't mean this doesn't hurt.
Kate...
What do I do now?!
How could I have been so awful to Kate?!
Still, I can't drag her into this.
Not Kate, of all people.
Miss Grail.
Your Lordship.
U-Um, thank you so much
for the other day.
What for?
For the investigative committee.
I see. She didn't mince words.
How like Abigail.
Yes. I'll have to pay her
a thank-you visit.
What could be the matter?
That's Kendall Levine,
a high-ranking diplomat.
He's a special envoy from Faris.
What could have him so flustered?
It sounds like they've lost
a member of their delegation.
Is Scarlett there?
Y-Yes. You see...
Ulysses?
Someone by that name
has been missing since yesterday.
Do you know him?
That's probably Ulysses Faris,
the nine-year-old seventh prince of Faris.
A p-prince?!
A kidnapping, perhaps?
How horrible.
In that case, why haven't
the Farisians said anything?
Pardon me, Miss Grail. I must—
Return to the Security Force, right?
Prince Ulysses is bound
to be terribly anxious.
Please find him as soon
as you possibly can.
I will. As for your meeting
with Crown Princess Cecilia...
I'll be careful.
Her Royal Highness won't
trip me up if I can help it.
If all else fails,
I'll use Your Lordship's name.
I may be no match for her
even then, but nevertheless...
Well said.
In any case...
I'm intrigued by who could possibly
abduct someone amid all this security.
Your intuition again?
We still have time.
I'll see what I can find.
Welcome!
Why, where's Randy?
I'm terribly sorry.
Urgent business called him away.
Too bad for him!
Now, have a seat! Have a seat!
I haven't had a guest
in this room in ages!
Did you learn anything?
I discovered one suspicious man.
Vado, a merchant
from the Republic of Soldita.
He came to see Cecilia.
Unusual, aren't they?
They came from all over the continent.
I have a merchant who finds them for me.
He's ever so good at his job.
Does this merchant... call on you often?
Yes. His name's Vado, by the way.
He was here just yesterday.
He came with a massive wicker hamper
on his back full of carpets to sell me.
But why do you ask?
N-No reason.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
The tea will get cold.
What a distinctive smell.
Oh, yours is ordinary black tea.
I used to be rather sickly.
Vado fetches me
this special herbal tea as a favor.
So, that's why we have separate pots?
Of course. Why else?
I'm terribly sorry.
The attempted poisoning of
Your Royal Highness is so famous,
I assumed you must
always be on your guard.
You mean Scarlett Castiel?
You speak as though
you know all about it.
No, I've only heard rumors.
Then I'll tell you the story.
That day,
Enrique reneged on
an appointment with Scarlett
in order to pay me a get-well visit.
She was furious.
That very night, we found that one
of our water jars had been poisoned.
Her earring lay beside the poisoned jar,
and a half-empty bottle of poison
was discovered in her home.
The rest happened just as you've heard.
She was executed for her crime.
But I am guilty of falling in love
with Enrique when I knew he was engaged.
And it's my fault that he has
no children. Poor Enrique.
I think he means to cede the throne
to Johan, his younger brother,
who has a son and a daughter.
Your Royal Highness...
Her woe-is-me act doesn't seem to have
won her any favor around here.
Take that herbal tea. It has poison
meant to terminate pregnancy.
If she's always drinking it,
it'd wreak havoc on her insides.
Her body must be as cold as ice.
Yes?
Oh, nothing! Just...
The thing is...
How stupid can you be?
Leave well enough alone.
Now you've made yourself a target.
But I couldn't just let
an unsuspecting person drink poison.
Oh? Did you ever consider
I might be making it up?
You may be a liar, Scarlett,
but I can still tell
when you're speaking the truth.
You've certainly gotten
cheeky lately, girl.
Now, about that merchant...
She said he was carrying a hamper.
Right.
You could hide a small child in that.
We'd better do a bit more digging.
How?
To learn of a professional,
ask someone in the same trade.
After all that,
we've learned Faris has a monopoly
on that abortion drug,
but no one knows this man named Vado.
My, my. No one knows a man
important enough to visit the palace?
That sounds like extremely valuable
information, if you ask me.
Do you really think so?
So sorry. Something seems
to be wrong with the rear wheels.
I'll just be checking on them.
C-Certainly.
Please pardon the delay.
As I feared, one of the rear wheels
is about to fall off.
Oh.
What's wrong?
He sounded... different.
The coachman's voice is different
from when we got in.
Is something the matter?
Why was the driver replaced?
Could this man be...?
A spell?
Yeah. For spotting bad guys.
If they react to it at all,
you'll know they're very bad people.
Kiriki kirikuku.
Stand aside!
Connie!
THE SILENT LADIES' TEA PARTY
Translation:
William Varteresian
Subtitle Timing:
Edgar Cruz
Subtitle Editing:
Riley Dalton
Quality Check:
SMR
Translation Check:
Sriram Gurunathan